<resources>

    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <!-- Basic Info -->
    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <string name="app_name">Soul Meds</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <!-- Sharing to Social Media -->
    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <string name="share_text">Check out this Bible verse from the Soul Meds mobile app</string>

    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <!-- Emergency & Meds Activities -->
    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <string name="bible_reference">Scripture quotations taken from the New American Standard Bible (NASB), Copyright 1960, 1962, 1963, 1968, 1971,
        1972, 1973, 1975, 1977, 1995 by The Lockman Foundation. Used by permission. www.Lockman.org</string>
    <string name="next_btn">Next</string>
    <string name="back_btn">Back</string>
    <string name="cancel_btn">Cancel</string>
    <string name="save_btn">Save</string>
    <string name="done_btn">Done</string>
    <string name="title_activity_emergency">Set Symptoms</string>

    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <!-- login & registration -->
    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign In</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login_register">Register</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_register">Register</string>
    <string name="action_login_navigate">Sign In To Existing Account</string>
    <string name="action_register_navigate">Create an Account</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <!-- Alarms Activity-->
    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <string name="title_activity_alarms">Prescription Manager</string>
    <string name="action_delete_item">Delete</string>
    <string name="action_edit_item">Edit</string>
    <string name="title_alarms_symptoms">Select a Symptom</string>
    <string name="title_alarms_times">Set Alarm</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="channel_id_alarms">AlarmsChannel</string>
    <string name="channel_name">Alarms</string>
    <string name="channel_description">Notifications for Prescription Alarms</string>

    <!-- ======================================================== -->
    <!-- Settings Activity -->
    <!-- ======================================================== -->

    <!-- General Settings Headers -->
    <string name="pref_header_tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="pref_header_change_prescriptions">Change Prescriptions</string>
    <string name="pref_header_change_alarms">Change Alarms</string>
    <string name="pref_header_reset">Reset Prescriptions &amp; Alarms</string>
    <string name="pref_header_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="pref_header_about">About</string>
    <string name="pref_header_email_support">Email Support</string>

    <!-- About Settings -->
    <string-array name="privacy_policy_array">
        <item><![CDATA[

        <br/>

        <h2>About</h2>

        <p>Effective date: September 24, 2018</p>
        <p>Soul Meds ("us", "we", or "our") operates the website and the Soul Meds mobile application (the "Service").</p>

        <p>This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service
        and the choices you have associated with that data. Our Privacy Policy for Soul Meds is managed through Free Privacy Policy.</p>

        <p>We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information
        in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Information Collection And Use</h2>

        <p>We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.</p>

        <h3>Types of Data Collected</h3>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h5>Personal Data</h5>

        <p>While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data").
        Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: </p>

        <ul>
        <li>Email address</li>

        <li>Cookies and Usage Data</li>
        </ul>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h5>Usage Data</h5>

        <p>We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data").</p>

        <p>This Usage Data may include information such as your computer\'s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type,
        browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.</p>

        <p>When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID,
        the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h5>Tracking & Cookies Data</h5>

        <p>We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.</p>

        <p>Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device.
        Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.</p>

        <p>You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies,
        you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.</p>

        <ul>
        <li><b>Session Cookies.</b> We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.</li>

        <li><b>Preference Cookies.</b> We use Preference Cookies to remember your
        preferences and various settings.</li>

        <li><b>Security Cookies.</b> We use Security Cookies for security purposes.</li>
        </ul>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Use of Data</h2>

        <p>Soul Meds uses the collected data for various purposes:</p>

        <ul>
        <li>To provide and maintain the Service</li>

        <li>To notify you about changes to our Service</li>

        <li>To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service
        when you choose to do so</li>

        <li>To provide customer care and support</li>

        <li>To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the
        Service</li>

        <li>To monitor the usage of the Service</li>

        <li>To detect, prevent and address technical issues</li>
        </ul>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Transfer Of Data</h2>

        <p>Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province,
        country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.</p>

        <p>If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data,
        to United States and process it there.</p>

        <p>Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.</p>

        <p>Soul Meds will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance
        with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate
        controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Disclosure Of Data</h2>

        <h5>Legal Requirements</h5>

        <p>Soul Meds may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:</p>

        <ul>
        <li>To comply with a legal obligation</li>

        <li>To protect and defend the rights or property of Soul Meds</li>

        <li>To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service</li>

        <li>To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public</li>

        <li>To protect against legal liability</li>
        </ul>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Security Of Data</h2>

        <p>The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100%
        secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. </p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Service Providers</h2>

        <p>We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to
        perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</p>

        <p>These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.</p>

        <h5>Analytics</h5>

        <p>We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.</p>

        <h6>Firebase<h6>

        <p>Firebase is analytics service provided by Google Inc.</p>

        <p>You may opt-out of certain Firebase features through your mobile device settings, such as your device advertising settings or by following the
        instructions provided by Google in their Privacy Policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=3Den</p>

        <p>We also encourage you to review the Google\'s policy for safeguarding your data: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245. For more
        information on what type of information Firebase collects, please visit please visit the Google Privacy &amp; Terms web page:
        https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=3Den</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Links To Other Sites</h2>

        <p>Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link,
        you will be directed to that third party\'s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.</p>

        <p>We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Children\'s Privacy</h2>

        <p>Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").</p>

        <p>We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your
        Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without
        verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Changes To This Privacy Policy</h2>

        <p>We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.</p>

        <p>We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date"
        at the top of this Privacy Policy.</p>

        <p>You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.</p>

        ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[

        <h2>Contact Us</h2>

        <p>If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at SoulMedsapp@gmail.com</p>

        ]]></item>

    </string-array>


    <!-- Tutorial Settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_rx">Rx button</string>
    <string name="pref_header_911">911 button</string>
    <string name="pref_header_folder">Folder button</string>


    <!-- Example settings for General -->
    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="set_alarms">Set Alarms</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="alarm_1">Alarm 1</string>
    <string name="alarm_2">Alarm 2</string>
    <string name="alarm_3">Alarm 3</string>
    <string name="pref_header_change_symptoms">Change Symptoms</string>
    <string name="symptom_1">Symptom 1</string>
    <string name="symptom_2">Symptom 2</string>
    <string name="symptom_3">Symptom 3</string>
    <string name="alarm_volume">Alarm Volume</string>
    <string name="set_symptoms">Set Symptoms</string>
    <string name="choose_symptoms">Choose Symptoms</string>
    <string name="choose_alarms">Choose Alarms</string>
    <string name="cross_image">cross image</string>
    <string name="continue_to_app">Continue To App</string>


</resources>
